export default [
    {
        question:
            'What is the highest-grossing film of all time without taking inflation into account?',
        optionA: 'Titanic',
        optionB: 'Avengers: Endgame',
        optionC: 'Avatar',
        optionD: 'Star Wars: The Force Awakens',
        correctAnswer: 'b',
    },
    {
        question: 'Who was responsible for the creation of the Night King?',
        optionA: 'The First Knight',
        optionB: 'The Dark Prince',
        optionC: 'The Children of the Forest',
        optionD: 'The Lord of the Woods',
        correctAnswer: 'c',
    },
    {
        question: 'What does “Valar Morghulis” mean in High Valyrian?',
        optionA: 'All men must die',
        optionB: 'All men must bow',
        optionC: 'All men must kill',
        optionD: 'All men must attack',
        correctAnswer: 'a',
    },
    {
        question: 'How many black keys are found on a traditional piano?',
        optionA: '32',
        optionB: '34',
        optionC: '52',
        optionD: '54',
        correctAnswer: 'a',
    },
    {
        question:
            'Which country has appeared in three World Cup finals but has never won?',
        optionA: 'England',
        optionB: 'Spain',
        optionC: 'Netherlands',
        optionD: 'Uruguay',
        correctAnswer: 'c',
    },
    {
        question: 'What is the warmest sea on Earth?',
        optionA: 'Dead sea',
        optionB: 'White sea',
        optionC: 'Red sea',
        optionD: 'Black sea',
        correctAnswer: 'c',
    },
    {
        question: 'What is the only major city located on two continents?',
        optionA: 'Reykjavik',
        optionB: 'Istanbul',
        optionC: 'Moscow',
        optionD: 'Madrid',
        correctAnswer: 'b',
    },
    {
        question:
            'Which one of the seven wonders of the ancient world is still standing?',
        optionA: 'Hanging Gardens of Babylon',
        optionB: 'Colossus of Rhodes',
        optionC: 'The Great Pyramid of Giza',
        optionD: 'Temple of Artemis',
        correctAnswer: 'c',
    },
    {
        question: ' What year did India gain its independence from Britain?',
        optionA: '1938',
        optionB: '1942',
        optionC: '1947',
        optionD: '1949',
        correctAnswer: 'c',
    },
    {
        question: 'In what month is Earth closest to the sun?',
        optionA: 'May',
        optionB: 'October',
        optionC: 'January',
        optionD: 'April',
        correctAnswer: 'c',
    },
    {
        question: 'How many new species continue to be discovered every year?',
        optionA: '16,000',
        optionB: '18,000',
        optionC: '32,000',
        optionD: '34,000',
        correctAnswer: 'b',
    },
    {
        question: 'Who invented Coca-Cola?',
        optionA: 'Asa Griggs Candler',
        optionB: 'Charles Elmer Hires',
        optionC: 'John Matthews',
        optionD: 'John Pemberton',
        correctAnswer: 'b',
    },
    {
        question: 'What is the only edible food that never expires?',
        optionA: 'White rice',
        optionB: 'Honey',
        optionC: 'Rye',
        optionD: 'Barley',
        correctAnswer: 'b',
    },
    {
        question:
            'What is the technical term for the “brain” of your computer?',
        optionA: 'Hard drive',
        optionB: 'RAM',
        optionC: 'CPU',
        optionD: 'Motherboard',
        correctAnswer: 'c',
    },
    {
        question: 'What was Google’s original name?',
        optionA: 'Googol',
        optionB: 'Oneshot',
        optionC: 'Typist',
        optionD: 'Backrub',
        correctAnswer: 'd',
    },
    {
        question:
            'What company did the founders of YouTube work for before starting YouTube?',
        optionA: 'Citi Bank',
        optionB: 'Stripe',
        optionC: 'PayPal',
        optionD: 'US Bank',
        correctAnswer: 'c',
    },
    {
        question: 'What was the number of Twitter’s original character limit?',
        optionA: '125',
        optionB: '135',
        optionC: '140',
        optionD: '280',
        correctAnswer: 'c',
    },
    {
        question: 'Who won the 2018 World Cup?',
        optionA: 'Germany',
        optionB: 'Portugal',
        optionC: 'Nigeria',
        optionD: 'France',
        correctAnswer: 'd',
    },
    {
        question: 'What is the fastest snake in the world?',
        optionA: 'Black Mamba',
        optionB: 'King Cobra',
        optionC: 'Boomslang',
        optionD: 'Taipan',
        correctAnswer: 'a',
    },
    {
        question: 'What’s the top number of a fraction called?',
        optionA: 'Denominator',
        optionB: 'Numerator',
        optionC: 'Decimal',
        optionD: 'Fractional',
        correctAnswer: 'b',
    },
]
